MAJA KUZMANOVA

CREATIVE WRITER

Profile

Creative Writer and Brand Namer with over 10 years of experience. Focused on creating short-form content, brand/business names, and slogans. Passionate about finding meaningful ideas, powerful words, and captivating concepts for every project. Combines a flair for language with an analytical mind and meticulous attention to detail.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCER

2014 - Present

- Named hundreds of businesses, brands, and products;
- Crafted tons of slogans and taglines;
- Created sentences that sell;
- Made content for different types of websites and social media channels;
- · Coordinated mailings, marketing materials, and website content for lifestyle websites;
- Updated tons of websites with new posts and made them SEO friendly;
- Took part in creating and organizing PR materials and events;
- Worked alongside marketing specialists and graphic designers;
- Outreached to potential clients;
- Provided excellent customer support to clients from different parts of the world;

RADIO HOST & AD WRITER

2010-2020, Radio 106, Bitola

- Anchored the morning show and edited audio files
- Created thousands of scripts and copies for ads and jingles;

CORE STRENGHTS

PROBLEM SOLVER

A client approached saying it would be impossible to register a trademark name for her ERP service. She said that all the good names are taken. After a few weeks of brainstorming, she had an ideal name, ready to be registered.

BELIEVING IN CHALLENGES

Whether it is a new software or learning a new language, I'm in. The fast learner in me likes to discover new points of view. The avid reader in me always has an excellent book recommendation as she keeps a pile of books on her nightstand.

GREAT IN COMMUNICATING WITH PEOPLE

The empathetic person in me is always willing to listen and offer fresh ideas and relevant solutions.



+38970317167



majamkuzmanova@gmail.com

EDUCATION

2007-2011

High School Josip Broz Tito, Bitola

2011 - 2014

Macedonian Institute for Media &

COURSES

- · Communications in Business Environment, Foundation Nikola Kljusev, Skopje
- Branding Foundations, LinkedIn
- Writing Ad Copy, LinkedIn
- Create a Brand Strategy, LinkedIn
- Create Your Brand Message Strategy
- Email Marketing, Hubspot

SKILLS

- Creative Writing
- Content Writing
- Copywriting
- Brand Strategy
- SEO
- Marketing
- Creative Thinking
- WordPress, Shopify, Joomla
- Audio Editing
- Canva
- Microsoft Office
- Google Suite
- Spanish (fluent)
- French (conversational)